McKelvey, Jean T. Papers /3001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- NYC-NYS (Box 29)
  - NYS PERB - Panel A-J, 1933-1947 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - NYS PERB - Panel K-Z, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - NYS PERB Panel - June '71 Restricted, Conf., 1971 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - NYS PERB Panel - June '71 Restricted + Confidential from black Binder, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - NYS PERB Panel - June '71 Restricted + Confidential from black Binder, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - NYS PERB Panel - June '71 Restricted + Confidential from black Binder, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - NYS PERB Panel - June '71 Restricted + Confidential from black Binder, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - NYS PERB Panel - June '71 Restricted + Confidential from black Binder, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - NYS PERB Panel - June '71 Restricted + Confidential from black Binder, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - NYS PERB Panel - June '71 Restricted + Confidential from black Binder, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - NYS PERB Panel - June '71 Restricted + Confidential from black Binder, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - NYS PERB Panel - Rules of Procedure (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - NYS - State University - Faculty Senate, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - NYS - State Univ. - Faculty Senate, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- O - US Department (Box 30)
  - Oxford/BNA Symposium, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Oxford/BNA Symposium, 1985-1988 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Oxford, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Public Employment Relations Research Inst., 1975 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Public Employment Relations Research Inst., 1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Public Empl. Rel. Res. Inst., 1972 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Rochester (NY) Committee in the Employment of Older Workers, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Rochester (NY) Dispute Settlement Center Advisory Bd., 1972 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Spidr - General, 1973-1978 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Misc., 1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Society of Professionals In Dispute Resolution SPIDR - General - 1973 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - SPIDR General '97, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - SPIDR - General '97, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - SPIDR - Liasm Comm. 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - SPIDR - Membership Roster, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Society of Professional In Dispute Resolution (SPIDR) Neutrals - 1971 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - SPIDR - Neutrals - 1971 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - SPIDR - Neutrals - 1971 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Stamford Univ. - Panel - 1971 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor Advisory Committee - Administrative, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor Advis. Comm., 1953 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. Administrator, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. Administration, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. - Athens, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. General, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. - General, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - US DOL Adv. Comm. Legislation, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - U.S. Dep. - Other Members, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. Publicity, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. Publicity, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. Working Papers, 1942-1953 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. Working Papers, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - US DOL Adv. Comm. Working Papers, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - U.S. DOL Adv. Comm. Working Papers, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- US President - Z (Box 31)
  - U.S. President's Review Committee on Employment-Management Relations in the Federal Service, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - USPRCE - Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, as amended, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - USPRCE - Executive Order 19088, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - USPRCE - Series of, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - USPRCE Summ. Of Testimony, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - USPRCE Summary of Recommendations by Committee, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum to Committee Members from Office of Sec. of Labor (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - USPRCE Letter of Labor Dept. to Cornell's Prof. Jean T. McKelvey, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - USPRCE Series of Staff Papers by President's Review Committee, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - USPRCE Letter from Lab Dept., 1968 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - USPRCE Staff Papers by Committee, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - USPRCE Letter from Labor Dept. to Prof. McKelvey, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - USPRCE Outline of the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - USPRCE Comparison of LMRDA (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - USPRCE Staff Papers by Committee, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - USPRCE Series of Administrative Confidential, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - USPRCE Letter from Dept. of Labor to Prof. McKelvey, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - USPRE Dept. of Justice memo re:, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - USPRCE Draft-Report of the President's Review Committee on Employee-Management Relations in the Federal Service, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - War Labor Board - General Appraisals, 1941-1944 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - War Labor Board (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - War Labor Board, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Wharton Sch. Conf. 1970 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - White House Conf. '62, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - White House Conf. '62, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - White House Conf. '62, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - White House Conf. '62, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - White House Conf. '72, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- A - Am A (Box 32)
  - ACME Markets 2/28/86 1 of 7, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - ACME Markets 2/28/86 2 of 7, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - ACME Markets 2/28/86 3 of 7, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - ACME Markets 2/28/86 4 of 7, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - ACME Markets 2/28/86 5 of 7, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - ACME Markets 2/28/86 6 of 7, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - ACME Markets 2/28/86 7 of 7, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Acoustical Materials 1 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Acoustical Materials 2 of 2, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Aeolian American Division of Aeolian Pianos Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Alleghany Airlines 1977 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Alleghany Airlines 1979 1 of 6 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Alleghany Airlines 1979 2 of 6 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Alleghany Airlines 1979 3 of 6 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Alleghany Airlines 1979 4 of 6 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Alleghany Airlines 1979 5 of 6 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Alleghany Airlines 1979 6 of 6, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Alleghany County, Port Authority of, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Industries, 1971-1974 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Industries 2 of 2, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation 1 of 4, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation 2 of 4, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation 3 of 4, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation 4 of 4, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation 1 of 4, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation 2 of 4, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation 3 of 4, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation 4 of 4, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - American Airlines 11/29/71 Smith, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - American Airlines 11/29/71 Smith, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - American Airlines 11/29/71 Smith, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - American Airlines 9/20/71 1 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - American Airlines 9/20/71 2 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - American Airlines 9/20/71 3 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - American Airlines 9/20/71 4 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - American Airlines 9/20/71 5 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - American Airlines 9/20/71 6 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - American Airlines 11/29/71 1 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - American Airlines 11/29/71 2 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - American Airlines 11/29/71 3 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - American Airlines 11/29/71 4 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - American Airlines 11/29/71 5 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - American Airlines 11/29/71 6 of 6, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - American Airlines 1972 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 1 of 14, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 2 of 14, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 3 of 14, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 4 of 14, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 48)
- Am A (Box 33)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 5 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 6 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 7 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 8 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 9 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 10 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 11 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 12 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 13 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - American Airlines 7/8/86 14 of 14, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 1 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 2 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 3 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 4 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 5 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 6 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 7 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 8 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 9 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 10 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 11 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 12 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 13 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 14 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - American Airlines 10/15/86 15 of 15, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Am C - Be (Box 34)
  - American Can Co. 1 of 3, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - American Can Co. 2 of 3, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - American Can Co. 3 of 3, 1950-1951 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - American LaFrance 3/80, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - American Machine and Foundry Company 10/16/64 1 of 4, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - American Machine and Foundry Company 10/16/64 2 of 4, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - American Machine and Foundry Company 10/16/64 3 of 4, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - American Machine and Foundry Company 10/16/64 4 of 4, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - American Optical Buffalo 1 of 5 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - American Optical Buffalo 2 of 5, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - American Optical Buffalo 3 of 5, 1978-1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - American Optical Buffalo 4 of 5, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - American Optical Buffalo 5 of 5, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Ansco 11/30/50 1 of 2, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Ansco 11/30/50 2 of 2, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Ansco 1952 1 of 4 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Ansco 1952 2 of 4 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Ansco 1952 3 of 4 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Ansco 1952 4 of 4 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Armco Steel Corporation 11/16/73 1 of 6, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Armco Steel Corporation 11/16/73 2 of 6, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Armco Steel Corporation 11/16/73 3 of 6, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Armco Steel Corporation 11/16/73 4 of 6, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Armco Steel Corporation 11/16/73 5 of 6, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Armco Steel Corporation 11/16/73 6 of 6, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Armstrong Cork Company 9/24/75 1 of 5, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Armstrong Cork Co. 9/24/75 2 of 5, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Armstrong Cork Co. 9/24/75 3 of 5, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Armstrong Cork Co. 9/24/75 4 of 5, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Armstrong Cork Co. 9/24/75 5 of 5, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Armstrong Cork Co. 9/3/74, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Batavia 1968 1 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Batavia 1968 2 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Batavia 1968 3 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Batavia 1976 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Batavia 8/11/80 1 of 5, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Batavia 8/11/80 2 of 5, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Batavia 8/11/80 3 of 5, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Batavia 8/11/80 4 of 5, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Batavia 8/11/80 5 of 5, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Batavia 10/31/83 1 of 5, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Batavia 10/31/83 2 of 5, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Batavia 10/31/83 3 of 5, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Batavia 10/31/83 4 of 5, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Batavia 10/31/83 5 of 5, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Beech-Nut Packing Co. 1 of 5, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Beech-Nut Packing Co. 2 of 5, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Beech Nut Packing Co. 3 of 5 1955 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Beech Nut Packing Co. 4 of 5 1955 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Beech Nut Packing Co. 5 of 5 1955 (Box 34, Folder 50)
- Be - Br (Box 35)
  - Behr-Manning Co. 9/6/62 1 of 3, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Behr-Manning Co. 9/6/62, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Behr-Manning Co. 9/6/62 3 of 3, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Bell Aerospace 1974 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Bell Aerosystems 1 of 4 9/67, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Bell Aerosystems 2 of 4 9/67, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Bell Aerosystems 3 of 4 9/67, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Bell Aerosystems 4 of 4 9/67, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 12/19/68 1 of 5 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 12/19/68 2 of 5 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 12/19/68 3 of 5 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 12/19/68 4 of 5 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Bell Aerosystems 12/19/68 5 of 5 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 4/70 1 of 2, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 4/70 2 of 2, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 9/70 1 of 7, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 9/70 2 of 7, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 9/70 3 of 7, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 9/70 4 of 7, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 9/70 5 of 7, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 9/70 6 of 7, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Bell Aerosystems Co. 9/70 7 of 7, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Bell Telephone of Pennsylvania 1982 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Bell Telephone of Pennsylvania 3/28/83 1 of 3, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Bell Telephone of Pennsylvania 3/28/83 2 of 3, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Bell Telephone of Pennsylvania 3/28/83 3 of 3, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Bendix Corp., 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Bergen-Kleifgen, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Blackstone Corp. 1 of 3, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Blackstone Corp. 2 of 3, 1949-1956 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Boise Cascade 7/3/85 1 of 6, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Boise Cascade 7/3/85 2 of 6, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Boise Cascade 7/3/85 3 of 6, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Boise Cascade 7/3/85 4 of 6, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Boise Cascade 7/3/85 5 of 6, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Boise Cascade 7/3/85 6 of 6, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Bongiovanni 1 of 3, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Bongiovanni 2 of 3, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Bongiovanni 3 of 3, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Borden Co. 1 of 2, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Borden Co. 2 of 2, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Borden Chemical Co., 1975 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Borden Ice Cream Co. 1963 1 of 4 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Borden Ice Cream Co. 1963 2 of 4 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Borden Ice Cream Co. 1963 3 of 4 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Borden Ice Cream Co. 1963 4 of 4 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Braniff Airways 1 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Braniff Airways 2 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 48)
- Br - Bu (Box 36)
  - Brighton 1 of 5, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Brighton 2 of 5, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Brighton 3 of 5, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Brighton 4 of 5, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Brighton 5 of 5, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Brighton CSD 1/75 1 of 4, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Brighton CSD 1/75 2 of 4, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Brighton CSD 1/75 3 of 4, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Brighton CSD 1/75 4 of 4, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Brighton CSD 1/75 1 of 3, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Brighton CSD 1/75 2 of 3, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Brighton CSD 1/75 3 of 3, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Brighton CSD 1/76 1 of 8, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Brighton CSD 1/76 2 of 8, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Brighton CSD 1/76 3 of 8, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Brighton CSD 1/76 4 of 8, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Brighton CSD 1/76 5 of 8, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Brighton CSD 1/76 6 of 8, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Brighton CSD 1/76 7 of 8, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Brighton CSD 1/76 8 of 8, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Brighton CSD 1/27/76 1 of 3, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Brighton CSD 1/27/76 2 of 3, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Brighton CSD 1/27/76 3 of 3, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Brighton CSD 12/76 1 of 1, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Brighton CSD 12/3/79 1 of 6, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Brighton CSD 12/3/79 2 of 6, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Brighton CSD 12/3/79 3 of 6, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Brighton CSD 12/3/79 4 of 6, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Brighton CSD 12/3/79 5 of 6, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Brighton CSD 12/3/79 6 of 6, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Brighton CSD 6/22/82 1 of 5, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Brighton CSD 6/22/82 2 of 5, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Brighton CSD 6/22/82 3 of 5, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Brighton CSD 6/22/82 4 of 5, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Brighton CSD 6/22/82 5 of 5, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Brighton CSD 3/12/84, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Brighton CSD ND 1 of 2, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Brighton CSD ND 2 of 2, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Brighton Place Diary, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - British Overseas Airways Corp. 1 of 3, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - British Overseas Airways Corp. 2 of 3, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - British Overseas Airways Corp. 3 of 3, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Brockport 1 of 5, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Brockport 2 of 5, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Brockport 3 of 5, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Brockport 4 of 5, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Brockport 5 of 5, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Brown Manufacturing Co., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Brunner Manufacturing Co. 1 of 2, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Brunner Manufacturing Co. 2 of 2, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1970 1 of 4 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1970 2 of 4 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1970 3 of 4 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1970 4 of 4 (Box 36, Folder 54)
- Bu (Box 37)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/6/71 1 of 6, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/6/71 2 of 6, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/6/71 3 of 6, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/6/71 4 of 6, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/6/71 5 of 6, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/6/71 6 of 6, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/23/71 1 of 4, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/23/71 2 of 4, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/23/71 3 of 4, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 9/23/71 4 of 4, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 1 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 2 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 3 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 4 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 5 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 6 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 7 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 8 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 9 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 10 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 11 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 12 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 13 of 26, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 14 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 15 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 16 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 17 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 18 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 19 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 20 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 21 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 22 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 23 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 24 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 25 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 2/7/73 26 of 26, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 8/74, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1975 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 5/27/76 1 of 4, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 5/27/76 2 of 4, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 5/27/76 3 of 4, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 5/27/76 4 of 4, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1976 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/8/78 1 of 3, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/8/78 2 of 3, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/8/78 3 of 3, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/83 1 of 1, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/15/83 1 of 4, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/15/83 2 of 4, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/15/83 3 of 4, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/15/83 4 of 4, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 51)
- Bu - Ca (Box 38)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/5/84 1 of 8, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/5/84 2 of 8, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/5/84 3 of 8, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/5/84 1 of 8, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/5/84 5 of 8, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/5/84 6 of 8, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/5/84 7 of 8, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 6/5/84 8 of 8, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1986 Central Office Staff (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1986 Farmer (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1986 Teachers (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 1986 Wrzesien (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. 12/14/87, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Buffalo Broadcasting 1 of 2, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Buffalo Broadcasting 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Buffalo, City of 1/79 1 of 6, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo, City of 1/79 2 of 6, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Buffalo, City of 1/79 3 of 6, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Buffalo, City of 1/79 4 of 6, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Buffalo, City of 1/79 5 of 6, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Buffalo, City of 1/79 6 of 6, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Buffalo, City of 1983 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Buffalo, City of Police Dept. 1 of 4, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Buffalo, City of Police Dept. 2 of 4, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Buffalo, City of Police Dept. 3 of 4, 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Buffalo, City of Police Dept. 4 of 4, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Buffalo Dept. of Health, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Buffalo Linen Supply 1 of 4, 1971-1974 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Buffalo Linen Supply 2 of 4, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Buffalo Linen Supply 3 of 4, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Buffalo Linen Supply 4 of 4, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Buffalo Sewer Authority 6/9/81 1 of 4, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Buffalo Sewer Authority 6/9/81 2 of 4, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 33)